Thanks for watching, and I'll see you in the next video!
The rhythm, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Jamie
Jamie last night. I think was pretty good. I don't know. I think he may have been I
Know I know I'm ghost is kind of rude, right?
You know
He doesn't mean he doesn't mean any harm. He doesn't
He was kind of rude and I know you're very protective of Paige and you know Alex and I didn't too
but I
Don't think they really took any offense
They did, I'll have a talking to them, but, you know, it's just, you know, he's a little bit
backwards now. So, you don't have to apologize. I know you're offended enough for them, right?
Got my big Mac today.
Right, you know what I think?
See if I think they had fun.
Everybody.
You also apologize.
And I'm sure they appreciate you looking out for them.
But you know.
Unfortunately, part of the internet is we're going to get some
childish behavior. Did you see what was going on in the chat last night? I mean,
some of the chats, some of the chat was on call four, but hey, what's up easy?
Everyone hear me okay? Yeah, it's pretty good. I'm kind of been addicted to McDonald's lately.
Hey, babe. Let's say hi to Trixie. Hi.
Oh, but, you know, Ghost, Spunky, you know, he, I don't think he really said anything
that bad.
But some of the chat was kind of rude, right, and we had Alex on and Ghost was a little
bit rude.
I just put him backstage for a little bit and he, he straightened up, but yeah, Mr.
I'm in a better mood though, you know. Yeah, you want some Big Mac? It's a pretty good Big Mac today.
So excuse me for eating a little bit on camera, but...
I gotta say, for someone with no, no supposed appetite...
I'm eating pretty good
Hmm, hope everybody's doing okay
Yeah, I've always been the skinny like I know and it's like I was thinking like
Because everyone's like oh my god, you look so skinny. It's because I've been wearing like t-shirts a lot lately. I've always been a skinny
But I spent the first six months kind of more
More kind of cover up like wearing my flannels and stuff like that. So I look a little bit bigger, but
Hey, this is me. I have like a Marilyn Manson build, right?
No, you see my tattoos and stuff
We're gonna have a good day
Yesterday was just a little bit moody. I needed I needed some naps
Okay, but they got enough naps. I
I was like, okay, let's try one more time, right?
I put on my, my Darmor sunglasses this morning, okay, there we go.
It's okay, I can look sick, you know, I'm actually really healthy.
If a sick person wouldn't be in such a good mood, a sick person would be like, oh, I gotta make it.
Hey, TravelingGypsy, good to see you.
Yeah, and you guys, you know, I am like under kind of like a little campaign right now
By trolls, it's gonna be a lot of the same people
Mods can just look out if anything like that out of line is said either you or me or something like that
Good to see you too darling
Then um, you know feel free to
Basically time people up for 24 hours. I know
You know we had
Some people getting hidden for you know, there's a lot of people that are just
From the troll community that are friends of mine, and they might be a little trollish
But um
But then there's some that are like kind of like my
If they've called themselves my enemy, so I'm not crying I'm fine Bronzeberg the Bronzeberg is a member
He's a member and calling like saying horrible things, but you know what Bronzeberg? I
I know you might be salty because I maybe kicked you off a panel and brought you back
on a couple of times, but you know, sometimes I'm a little sensitive.
I don't know why you're so angry at me, but hopefully we can work things out.
I'm not mad at you.
I know.
It's hard to keep everybody happy, right?
Salty because I well, it's like there's a reason because you used to like my show used to be on used to be
Well, go ahead give me an example broadsword of that. I want to hear I want to hear your evidence or an example
Yeah, did I do something to you that I hurt your feelings that I defend you or something because you just turned on me kind of and
I'm curious to know what I did because maybe I can like make it up to you
But if not, you know, I can't please everybody
So if I just want to apologize if I did something hurt your feelings or defend you or offend you or something
I'm a backstabbing piece of shit. Okay, but I just want you and to all your friends
But just give me an example though. I want to hear the example. I
Want to hear what did I do?
Because it's like I mean people are calling me names and stuff, but I don't hear any evidence or like backing it anything up
I just hear a lot of accusations. Am I saying I'm tough? Look at me. This is my muscle. Am I saying I'm that tough?
I'm like a skinny nerd, right?
No, I won't I won't mod him. He's a he's a member though
I think he got it's game over campaign for life
But you wait so you finally found some exceptions and like what the CFF or something like that like what's the what what uh?
Don't let me catch you another panel well bronze bird it's already been worked out
I've already talked to some people about you and stuff like that and they know what to look for
Pizza's at my door. Well, can you pay for them at least okay? Not very cool to send a pizza to my door
Not pay for them because all I have to do is tell the Mexican pizza lady. No, I'm sorry
Miss a prankle
No, she ain't so and then she gets a free pizza
so maybe they like you because they're being free pizzas, but I
Had the broke one. Okay
The broke one sitting here in my apartment
That I've been sitting into the start of the show. I'm not it's not gonna go back. It's worth me broadsburg, you know
Watch, okay
Well, is that talking shit guys? Did you hear me talking shit to him?
Okay
Yeah, I don't care if you'd send a pizza to my door if you pay for
If you don't pay for it, you expect me to pay for the pizza that I didn't order you got another thing coming
I won't answer the door. I won't even I have a little note of my door saying, you know
I've got some assholes between print calls of pizza places if it's not paid for I'm sorry
Enjoy your free pizza pizza person
You can go think think Bronzeberg. Oh, sorry to see that for whoever is attacking me today
Okay, well guys
I mean crying I didn't I remember shedding ones here, but you can go keep them around but if I get emotional
Together have an emotional side. I'm in touch with my feminine side, which is sometimes the notice the emotional side
Are you in touch with your emotional side? You're coming inside Bronzeberg?
Or are you repressing it?
I fear that your
Your gay feelings are gonna come out the last few panels. No
Whatever wrongs you I made you laugh at least feminine side. Okay, so you're saying women are just
Wow
Women are women exemplify the feminine, right? So you're calling all women that that's not very nice
And that's not a good way to get the females on your side either. You're just psycho. Okay
Okay, well guys, he's fine and mods leave Bronzeberg alone, you know, he's a
They'll come around if you like it really if you get to know me you will probably like me
but
You know, maybe I can't win everybody over I'd like to at least to say like I'm not a bad person
That's what I want to know sassy like if I did something I'm sorry I said I
Remember I think maybe hey, what's up Amanda a couple of times I might have put him backstage
You know, I I put ghost backstage a couple times last night
I mean I reserve the right to run my panel like I want to it doesn't not anything against anybody
It's just I
Don't know I'd like him to explain it like if you know if you have a problem just go ahead and bring it to my attention, right?
What happened to my channel? Nothing last night had over 60 people in my chat. I think 63 peaked out
63 maybe
You all see it these guys. Does anyone know what he's talking about though anybody?
Jamie so Jamie's still a bit salty. Well, Jamie
Ghost is person that's his personality. It's okay. Jamie but
Yeah, I mean, you know ghost was a little bit rude like he always is and I put it backstage a few times
He said he's in love with page and stuff, I mean
He really it's like ghost is like the fifth grader. That's like
They you know pulls on the pigtails of the girl he has a crush on right just to get her attention
He was very rude to Alex. Yeah
But I put him backstage, right and I really don't like to do that
But I did a few times and then he would you know, let me know hey
I'm uh, I'm sorry. I'm not gonna do that. I was crying about how I'm in my feeling. Well, sometimes I might be
Like I said, I'm a human being too and it sometimes hurts some of the things people say
Especially when people believe them, right? I'm getting all kinds of shit, right?
Well bronze your last night you me got unmodded, you know
For racism. I didn't see what she said about you and betas. I already left at that point, but
Be didn't I are cool. I
Think I'm cool with everybody. Okay
Yeah, we have good and bad days and guys I I wear my car in my sleep sometimes
I'm not gonna apologize for it. It's my personality
didn't delete those lives where I'm kind of like I know it's isn't it a lot
Amanda it's a lot of arguments and stuff but then you talk your shit yeah
mods you really don't have to delete anybody today or even you know but let
people talk their shit get it out maybe they're gonna get other system I feel
tough cuz I'm on my own stream well
You know, isn't it called when you play football, isn't it called home team advantage or like, you know, people like to play football on their own
Field, right? I don't know
Maybe bronzes and understand, you know, the mail sports
Right, you don't understand the concept of home team advantage
Like it's more comfortable when you're on your own territory than it's like you're going somewhere else and being attacked by people
I don't know
Bronze you may want to watch some footballs. Okay. I'm talking to you right now
I'll step up to you. You want me to go on your show? That's that I haven't been on your show. That's it. Okay
Bronze
What did I say I'd be this about you what did I say you came up on panel started attacking me and I just left
Obviously you do bronze because look who you just said
You want me to be on your your show, right? I'll go to your show bronze go ahead and promote or
Okay, let a mod. I know your channel name. You're not a mod. You can't post anything
Okay, bronze bronze
See I win got two W's
You're just like making yourself look kind of dumb, but that's what I'm going to let people do.
They can just reveal themselves and then everyone else can be the judge of it.
I'm not going to lose sleep over it. Say whatever you want. I'm not hiding you,
I'm not running from you. I'm trying to address you.
You're dumb because you're the guy making any sense.
There you go sassy. Thank you
There's bronzes channel goes ahead of bronze bird on his show. Maybe I'll make it soon. Okay
You're better than me, okay, maybe you are maybe I'm the worst person in the world, right?
Guys I will not be bringing anybody up on stage unless they are on camera
Yeah, because I wear I wear flannels and so I've been wearing these t-shirts. So this is how skinny I am
It's okay
I didn't I didn't but that I didn't get my channel back that that that troll lied and didn't keep as part of the bargain
Right. I was happy to dance some wild horses or whatever the the song is. I don't care if I dance like this for a second
I think for $15 you didn't have data
Right because I wanted to go to the pier and I wanted to get fish tacos at the pier that day. That was like six months ago
Okay, let's bring up six months ago
No, I'm gonna call your kindergarten teacher and and find out information about you
Bronze word got beat up on the playground by a bunch of girls
Wow guys
Disreveal yourself wrongs. Just reveal yourself keep revealing yourself keep doing it. Please just reveal yourself
Abedic
Anyone scared bronze if I can if I can survive the CFF I can survive bronze bird your little chicken
Your bronze chicken
What you can do is talk shit in the chat room my chat room by the way
Good night, Amanda. You have a good rest. I
Can't I can't survive shit. I haven't missy
How many months have we been almost a year on YouTube? I'm fine. I'm monetized
Okay, well, you know what you're talking too much in the chat, or I think you just need a little breakie
Come back when you're
After your nap time, okay? I need a nap sometimes. I know bronze does use a little nap because he's like I basically a kindergarten
So bronze come back later
He's overtaking the chat, okay?
So he just needs a little breaky.
He needs a little nap time.
Jamie I thought it was a great stream. You didn't hear like Alexandra and Summer and Paige all having a great chat.
I remember that. I remember.
Jamie you see what's going on with other people sometimes you've been in some of the streams
Okay, he wants to talk his shit on on the panel, so I'll let him hold on
The days of Monday hold on one second
Hello yo, yeah, what's wrong you were pussy, okay
Oh, you think you think that you're gonna be able to talk shit when it comes to me and then think that I was gonna run up here and talk shit
You don't have no backbone. You never did you're a skinny punk ass bitch
What I say punk ass bitch
Allow me to speak about you. What is it? You want me to say it? You want me to say it or you gonna shut the fuck up?
Tell me what I said about you. You want me to say it or you gonna keep talking?
You act as if you didn't say what you said in beaters and I caught you talking shit
And the thing about it is is that you think you so fucking tough
You've never been tough on these YouTube streets
You're a pussy and we all know it and the thing about it is you think you getting off on what the fuck you do your
Fraud a liar and a manipulator and I know what the fuck you about psyche
You can go lie and cry me you can go lie and cry on other people's strings
We ain't fooled by what the fuck you about tell me you're a liar
You're a fucking you're a fucking lion deceiver you sack of shit and every single time see how you cry for the last couple of days
You cry for the last couple days. He's like, oh, you know, I think everybody hates me and blah blah blah
It's gonna get worse for you psych. You trust me. That's my word
Everything you talk all that shit
You're a pussy you're a real pussy
Dirty ass fingernails and all that shit pussy get the fuck out of here
Psyche that's why you ran a tiktok because people wasn't supporting you you fucking pussy
You're a fucking pussy tell me tell me you can get off my dick just like Apollo
Both of y'all is pussy all you talk is shit psyche you fraud
You're a pussy. You're a pussy now. You want to be on some racist shit about me being black just like you me
You just like you me and I just caught you
Just caught you now you want to be on some racist shit like you me now
You want to be on some racist shit like you me now you want to be on some racist shit like you me exactly you a pussy
Watch bro. We cool bro
Keep eating that burger with your skinny ass. You need to gain some weight fuck boy the fuck out of here you pussy
Well, you let trolls take over your stream and you don't do shit about it cuz you don't know what else to do
You're a cloud chaser
example
Like I said, I said all examples. I've been said about you
Read it back. Read it back. Read it back. You're a clout chaser
Emma don't fuck with you and Jordana don't fuck with you. You know that
She doesn't fuck with you. Yes, she does. When she showed up to your camera when she showed up to your panel
Well, she's a good panels. She's a good other exactly. She never
What about Emma? What about Emma? What about Emma? Yeah?
Misunderstanding that Emma never Emma never came to your panel fam
I interviewed her. You begged for motherfuckers to come on your channel
That's why and when motherfuckers don't come to your channel
You run like a bitch to the panel to sit up there and ask for forgiveness. You a bitch
That's why we all know that shit
The fuck out of here psyche. You're a fraud a liar and a manipulator
You're a liar
And then you so thirsty for money you sit up there shit on your friends you fucking backstabbing piece of shit
Wow one example though. Give me an example. You already know the example
So tell me I already know that everybody else tell everybody else
Or shut up Fred go ahead go ahead
Already told you bro. How many times I'm not gonna keep repeating what the fuck I said, you know
You ain't got shit to say go ahead cry cry like you did the last couple of days
I'm gonna see you on beat a stream crying like a bitch watch
He ran like a little girl. Okay. No, I don't yeah anyway, he ran like a little
The little little baby. Okay. Anyway
What did he get anything guys they convinced everybody
Yeah, you me well, he means not up, you know, you me I don't have anything against you you me it was like I asked you not to
do the racial stuff and
You me did but you know what?
You'll be fine and just in the chat, okay?
But I don't know guys is that is everyone convinced I mean
Bronzeberg
Pretty weak a little bit weak
Okay
All right guys all right a little bit weak
Do you agree or not?
I mean, here, there's my stream yard.
Come on up if you feel like talking.
Okay, so I'm altering the sponsored panel thing
a little bit, because I think people misunderstand it.
I'll do sponsored panels still,
but basically I'm just gonna do open panels.
I won't require anybody to sponsor a panel
for me to open an open panel, but if you do want.
Your ad if you have an ad or something and you'd like it to be on the scroll during the panel
You're welcome to run an ad on my show. That's all I have to say and it will be on the scroll
I'll have somebody in them. I'll have them on put your link in the chat and
It'll be like 10 bucks if you want for like three hours
You'll have your ad on the screen and stuff like that. I think it's pretty reasonable for advertising
Um, you know, even, you know, even my enemies, I can go to some of my enemy's chats and I see a lot of people in here
in my enemy's chats because I promoted my enemies, even my enemies, and it's like, so
if even, like, I can bring business to my enemies, imagine the business I can bring to my friends, okay?
So, is that a better idea? I think it's a better idea.
Yeah, so, yeah.
I mean guys some people are just a little bit sad. Isn't it sad?
Anyway
I came here in a good mood
Wanted to like chat and have a good time
You can see what people come here try to bring down the vibe and stuff. It's fun
because I have a high enough vibe to
handle it
So no harm no foul except the big big bronze chicken squawking away
Okay, anyway, let's have a fun day though. I got some
Good stuff to talk about today
Okay, so first of all I found my VR my VR controllers
I was like, where could they be?
I was like, it's impossible for things to disappear.
And it is, things don't disappear.
They're just put where you don't remember.
It's searched through everything.
I did find them.
Hopefully my VR does work.
I'm going to try today to see if I can get it running.
My computer should be able to run it
because it's a sticky computer.
But, you know, how's everyone doing?
27 people in chat.
Yeah, go ahead.
Love me or hate me.
You know, hit the like.
How about my algorithm, you know, but I just want to talk to anybody that wants to have
a chat.
Maybe I'll do a shorter stream today, I don't know, I'm going to come back on later, but
you know, because I don't want to spend all this energy on the people talking shit because
they're just going to come talking shit and get me to expend my energy and then I get
sleepy.
I'm here to have fun here to help you have fun. I'm just here to entertain basically
No one's required to thank you, Tonya. No one's no one's uh
forced to donate or
You know support my channel or become a member or anything as long as you're here, right?
Hey, Hebrew hammer, how are you? Good to see I haven't seen you for a while
You're welcome to come on panel if you want
Anybody want to come up? I do have the link pinned
I'm willing to talk about anything you want to tell me off. You want to call me a piece of you know, sh it
You want to say anything you want about me? Oh, I'm willing to
To talk to you no one's gonna get timed out today mods, you know, just unless it's really really slanderous or something
Doxing or something like that. Go ahead and just keep people here
I'm gonna have everybody have the freedom to speak
Got a little bit more energy today to deal with this and so
They're good. Okay. Let me see you're good. You start off work. Okay. That'd be cool. Oh
He's like to talk to Hebrew hammer
Jamie well, you know, Jamie why are you so fixated on ghosts?
I mean you see some other people actually are rude to me be rude to you ghosts is like ghost knows
He's a little bit of a
Shitster or whatever, but you know
He's not a bad person, you know, you know how like, you know, how Jamie, you know, you like God, I like Tommy Goddy, too, you know
Even no matter what he said about me the pictures he puts up of me and
Spurting rumors that you know that I have different diseases and coming on a million accounts
I still like the person and you like him, right?
You're over there. You had no problem with anything he was saying about me and the other chat. So
You know, why am I gonna worry about what ghost says when people are perfectly capable of handling those cells that I did
I didn't kick them off the panel for a few times, but
You know, whatever anyone wants to say they can
I'm very into freedom of speech
I'm a libertarian which is like basically, you know, I want freedom
I don't like people misusing the freedom by putting slanders, accusations, and doxing and things like that.
I don't like racial language. I have it on my show. No racial bigotry and stuff.
I don't know what else I can do. Let me see. I can put it up on the screen.
I think this has been my rule since I started the show.
Excuse me. Let me see.
He says no hate speech that's been I was like the one of the first rules no hate speech right there. No doxing
Respect the host and other panelists if they don't I had the right to kick them off
Okay
Am I doing something wrong guys like let me know, you know, but I really rather hear from my friends than my enemies if I'm
Screwing up. So Jamie it's like I take it personally when you say, oh, I let you know this person do this and this
Because you know we're friends and you're like my my first mod and stuff, right?
So if you have a real problem, you you know
You know how to contact me personally, right?
And anybody can I do have my links up?
Um
What else I do want to say guys if you don't have a
You know, I do want to like maybe like
promote myself a little bit in certain ways so cash app is having a promotion for new sign-ups and
I just want to share my cash at blink
This is for signing up there. I think you get something too. You can go check it out
I'm just going to share this link if you're interested in
in a
Cash up account. They're free accounts. They're really cool. I would say a
good way to send receive money and
So go check. I'm not sure what the bonus they're going to give you but here's the link and so go ahead and
Yeah
And you'll get a $5 when you send $5 you'll get $5, okay?
So that's the that's a way for you to make some money too, okay?
I'd say it's a really really cool website and that's how I prefer to like a lot of you know donations
They send you a debit card and you know instant so
It's a little bit faster than some methods
So that's my little commercial for the moment if you're interested in that
But again, it's up to you most people already have an account or something like that, but
There you go
Everyone's doing good though. I want to make sure everyone's good. I got I also have on my on my linked page
Something called the my Amazon influencer page. I'm gonna be adding some stuff. I got an Amazon for example
I got this soap. This is called reversal soap. It's by Oli way
these are very
Why is it an account instead of username because YouTube is doing that for some reason in some chats?
They test new things. They've been doing it for a few years. I don't know why it's on mine now, but
It kind of does help with the
identifying who people are because we do get some trolls so I don't really mind it
that much. You can also change that name every 15 days or two weeks and so go
into your settings you can change your name to whatever you want if you'd like
to. It is kind of weird I don't know why they do it go to go ahead into a go
ahead and go to Reddit they have some conversations about it like and people
Or I'm trying to dox anybody or anything. It's just how YouTube is choosing to do it. Okay
Hey, Spunky
Hey J-Dog
Yeah, Spunky. Spunky, I'm not sure if I did I get unblocked in your chat yet. I'm not quite sure but I heard you know
And there's somebody in your chat that wants to turn me straight.
I don't know.
She's going to have good luck with that.
Also, guys, I'm not sending her inappropriate messages or anything on this person that's
saying you're going to see somebody say, oh, he's harassing this person.
No, I'll share all my DMs with the person if you want me to do it again to prove that
I was just being nice and cordial.
I didn't say one of an inappropriate thing.
Yeah, JT blocked me a couple days ago in your chat, so I, you know, if you want to make
me a mod there, it's just standard moderators, so I'm a little bit protected.
That'd be cool, but I understand it's whatever you want to handle it, because I do like to
be in your chat and stuff.
Blocking me wherever they find me
For their mods and stuff like that. So I didn't do anything or say anything inappropriate
You can look at my message history in your chat. I didn't attack anybody or anything
Thank you, and I can walk you through it too spunky
Because it took me a little bit a while to figure out you have to go to YouTube studio just go on on a
Google
Search YouTube studio then you have to go in the web web version of it
And what I had fun last night too
We have to go and then you have to go to a community moderation
And you'll see a block list of where the who the mods have locked and stuff. You can just take them, you know
Take me off of there
Or anybody else on there that you know, you didn't hide and stuff because
Sometimes there's road mods that are not operating in your interest but in their own interest and but I'm definitely gonna be
You know pleasant and
Beget myself in any chat
If ghost comes over, please unmod me love the channel, but I'm not going to be a
Who are you talking about Jamie like her chat? Just goes over there. It's okay. Swammy. It's okay. You know, I'm not and
You're just a skinny guy
It's so funny like you know if somebody weighs 500 pounds people say oh, yeah
They just ate too much or blah blah blah if somebody's too skinny. They're like oh my god
You have a disease you look like you know your Auschwitz and all this kind of like really cool things
I don't know even like 600 pound person doesn't get picked on as much as I do for big skinny
And spunky really you don't have to block ghosts
I don't know why Jamie's all up in I've got her panties in a bunch about ghost ghost is a good guy
He's he just he likes to
He likes to, uh, debate, for the sake of debating, he's not very good, he, you know, he kind of exposes himself as kind of like just the, you know, just the, I don't know, he doesn't do anything that bad, but I mean, I would say if he does, then feel free to block him, but not just because, I mean, I'm going to defend Ghost because he's like a brother to me, so.
Like so Alex is nice, but I kept taking him off and Alex was like bring him back on and Alex is like
I like you and then he's like I like you too
And so not necessarily just because people couldn't go back and forth doesn't mean
They don't like each other right
I love Alex. I love Alex. We were talking about Alexandra who was on the show last night. Just a really awesome person
Super interesting conversations about what are really what things I like to talk about
We have actually the same birthday, you know, we're a couple years apart, but we have the same birthday
So we really vibe and stuff
So but again, I'm not gonna make everyone happy and there's gonna he doesn't mean any harm
I mean to like use like a
You know, I love you Jamie. It's like I just you know, you don't have to
Be mad at ghost what happened to Alex? He just doesn't come around anymore. I don't know what's going on with him
He doesn't come around much anymore
Last time I mean he keeps
Doing things that make me kick off him off the panel they kill
He pretty verbally abusive especially the female people
Friends of mine, so Alex NYPD is like a little bit
You know where I'm over saying his welcome or it's going too far, but if he behaves himself, I'm happy to have him back on I
Probably will just do an hour today. I'm gonna probably try to test my VR stuff later this afternoon
He don't want us to be a pool of card. You don't want to come on the panel
You guys are all welcome here. I'm here with tricks. Oh
Good boy
He did
I had to look at everyone and delete him.
Why was I asleep and he goes to abuse everyone?
I thought it was just Summer and if you went too far,
I think Alex had a good time though.
She wrote, I got a message this morning.
She had a great time on the panel.
So she didn't say anything about ghosts at all.
So I don't know.
And Summer also is friends with them.
Maybe like they they can talk to each other like that. I don't know if summer will let me know if you went too far
too
But I didn't hear I have I'm both I'm in private messages this summer and you know
If she had a problem sure she would let me know about it
Okay
So let's not make a mountain out of a molehill. It's just you know, it was his birthday yesterday. He
You know her birthday yesterday or yeah
This is birthday yesterday, so, you know, I kind of...
Oh, Alex, NYPD came under different accounts.
Okay, yeah, Alex. Oh, that, Alex, okay.
Yeah, I'm not sure. I'm not 100% sure. I did fall asleep.
Because I was kind of tired yesterday, but, yeah.
Okay, Jamie
Maybe he was mad because he could get on panel, but I was asleep so I can't add anybody when I'm asleep, you know
Unless I saw me listen, which means sleepwalking
Okay
I don't know. I think it got a little bit to focus on negativity again this stream.
It's unfortunate, but I'll save for another minute like right now and then
I'll come back later.
Okay, yeah, each case is a good mod. But yeah, bronze came in, firing.
I think some of the negativity turns off some people.
But anybody got anything to say or I just want you guys to know I'm still here. I love you
I know I'm moody sometimes
Hey, what's up time good to see ya
Yeah, I'm doing that. Okay. We have a guest. Let me see. Oh, Rudy's in the way
Who's there that Hebrew hammer that is?
The second we just covered the hey Rudy, come on here. I can't see the can't see my screen, babe. Hold on
That doesn't like keep your hammer. Hold on
Screen up real quick
Hello, hey, what's up psych? It's me. Hey, what's up? Hold on. Let me check on my thing. How are you today?
Good, I thought I would just come up because it seems like it's me like you can do some buddy
I don't know if you're bored or what?
How are you?
Good
We see yeah, that sounds good. Okay. Yeah, I don't hear an echo anymore
So you're yeah, I'm gonna see you for a little bit. How are you doing? Oh nice the nice picture. I'm good. Thanks
I just saw that like a lot of people are like turning like are just acting differently
It's not like my it's not my
My regulars if I'm I'm actually under attack by a certain little
Internet gang they come on under a million aliases. They've been saying really horrible things like I have HIV
Blah blah blah blah blah blah
Bring negativity to it. I've talked them in the act of talking about me behind my back like
To their face and so they're kind of salty right now. Just got gonna deal with it
But I don't think people are really turning. I mean some people might take what they say seriously, but you know
Get to know them get to know me. You'll see who's the the real
Real jerk is right gotcha
Okay
Okay, we have another guest on but I'm not sure who that is can I see?
Guess who's backstage? Can you please cam up so I can see you just backstage for a second
Just to prove that you're a real person and then I'll bring you up. Otherwise, I can't bring up people that I don't know
but
anyhow
Yeah, it's been a little bit a little bit negative and I'm just trying to turn it around
Which I can do I can I can always make a negative to a positive
so
Yeah
Yeah, I mean
It happens
What do you see in particular that kind of got you thinking that people are turning on me?
Well, maybe not. I mean, I just feel like people are just
No, no, they're like in this attitude lately. Okay, I don't know what's going on
Like there's like a strike war like on my side of YouTube
There's like a huge strike war where like people are like looking for everything and anything to strike each other
So everybody's like not going live
Yeah, it's been kind of slow and like
I just think it's kind of child a child this shit. Oh it is and it's like and I've had people threaten
I mean, I've actually had people do that to me before and you know, but uh, I
Think YouTube basically understands and it's like people that continue to do it YouTube starts to ignore them
Okay, proud of Babylonia. Let me just check this person. I'll see if they're here. Hold on
I might be a real person. Let me just check. They might say that they say the n-word. Hold on. Hello
Hey, how's it going? Hey, how are you?
I'm doing great. How are you doing? Pretty good. Okay. You're a real person. Hey Babylonian
We're here with Hebrew hammer and
proud of Babylonian. I got some cool
Guys, that's a cool names
Yeah, what's up today?
I'm drinking some cheap beer
You get some cheap beer cool
I'm drinking some kind of extensive beer. Well, I haven't drinking it yet, but I got a harder lemonade
Let me see. There we go. I got a harder lemonade and I got a
smirnoff ice smash
pineapple
Pineapple coconut. Yeah, that sounds good. Nice
Pineapple condo sounds interesting
Yeah, it's tasty and it's like a 8% alcohol. So it's kind of stronger and ahead of that good
sweet
coconut taste to do it so
I've been really cutting down on drinking lately. Remember I used to be on and kind of like a
totally drunk all the time and so
this is just me a little bit buzz if I have a couple and
I'm kind of controlling my drinking a little bit better. Isn't that one that's one of the great things about the internet
You can get fucking drunk in shitface. You don't have to drive
You can talk to all types of people that they may smell like shit, but you can't smell it cuz it's over the internet
Right. Well, it's true. And it's like also, you know, this is kind of like my job, you know
And so it's like I'm able to get shit based on my job, which is kind of like
Sometimes helps the show sometimes maybe like, you know, like I got a little bit too drunk. It's not that great
I especially if I pass out, but I
Don't know. I like I like to enjoy myself and
party in my stream a little bit, so
Yeah, that's one thing. I love about the internet and this thing is you know, you can get fucked up talk crazy and
It should be fun, right? But a lot of people are just scandalous and
Deviant so that part of human nature comes over like overwhelms a lot of shit a lot of times
Yeah, especially because people can just hide behind their, you know, big sock accounts or
You know a lot of the people don't even get up get on panel to discuss if they just do it from the chat
And you know they can just yell from the chat. They get two out of line. I can
basically just sit I'll throw up to the abyss and silence them, but I
Really want to avoid doing that. I just like people to get along basically and I like to convert my haters to fans
I've done that to some people, but so that's like alchemy, right?
Is that like a form of alchemy?
Exactly because alchemy is not just like you know changing metals like a like a base metal into gold
It's also about taking negative turning into positive having negativity work for you instead of against you
And you know changing darkness into light
Yeah, you turn the hater into a fan dude. I would say that's alchemy
Yeah, and I am and I am into spiritual alchemy and
You know, that's a form of it. I hope everybody can learn some lessons about that. It's like, you know, any negativity
even I was able to monetize some negativity sometimes on the panel and
That's like a win-win. They get to be themselves and be negative and I get to
I get to benefit from it too, so
you know
Yeah, usually haters are fans. Yeah, right Hebrew
Like they're here watching like there's a lot of people that watch that are silent in the chat
Maybe they're hate watching or something, but they are helping the the algorithm by just being here. So
Appreciate it appreciate it. Thank you
Things about this whole thing is like family like you can define fans however you want but
There's hate fans. That's crazy, dude. Like
I understand that you said that the algorithm more more fucking eyes more watchers equals more better for fucking you like
in a lot and
So many times. It's just your fucking here. So you can't block your fucking haters, but
Yeah, well, I mean I have but they usually have multiple accounts and they're just right back. It's kind of like a losing game. Oh, yeah
I block
Don't my main channel blocked all the motherfuckers talking shit because I'm that's not I'm not trying to talk to motherfuckers like
They don't have intellect. They can't say anything intelligent and all they say is something fucking whack-ass shit. They don't even make sense
Yep, I mean I'm kind of like letting them just reveal themselves down and people can make up their own mind about
who's who's right who's wrong and
You know, I'm gonna stop letting it bother me so much
I am kind of sensitive and when some some things are hurtful that are said but
If they figure out that they affect me that they're just gonna double up on it. It's just
Just makes it worse for me. So I'm just basically gonna kind of deal with it a different way, right?
So you never show your hand when it comes to trolls and don't feed them for sure, right?
They're looking for reaction. They're looking to trigger you they get a high from me being triggered and stuff and so
Once they find in the satisfaction once they find that thing that bothers you they're gonna they're definitely gonna attack that
Yeah, cuz they want they feel that high again, dude, and that's a great. Yeah, they
The great way to put it, dude, they're good. They get a high off of triggering you and so they're gonna look for it again
Yeah, it's basically like a narcissist again. What are narcissists after narcissists are after fuel after some kind of
Fuel to you know, they feel like they're empty like an empty gas tank in a car the fuel gets them going and so
You got to stop like you know providing the fuel
Didn't just go on to somebody else
But I'd rather them go to me than like you know my friends or you know, even people
I don't know that or maybe less equipped to deal with it because I know it can be you know, it can be
hurt hurtful and it can be grating and
You know, like a vampirism this can just take away some energy for the positive vibes. And so I'm gonna try to see more positive
You got to shake it off. You can't let it direct your
Your thought your thoughts are shit
Some people some people get
Overwhelmed and sink beneath the and they suffocate, you know beneath the level they can't come back up rare, dude, right?
True and uh, but I'm gonna let them reveal themselves. Hey, what's up? Empress Janet? How are you good to see ya?
Yeah, but I'm feeling better today. I just had a nice McDonald's McDonald's meal and uh
Wanted to come on and see what's up, and it's good to see you guys like you're having some friendly
friendly face. I grew I grew to love McDonald's man. Oh
the survey the buy one get one free survey dude what I love to do or what I
used to love to do but the whole location location location thing um that
the you know this buy one get one free survey do you can get a fucking double
quarter parent with cheese for like five something six dollars dude found
Pretty good. Good. Good afternoon. We're here with Hebrew hammer and Babylon proud Babylonian
Yeah, sorry I fell asleep last night summer but uh
Yeah, we had fun and then we went over on my panel for a little bit for like an hour
Then everybody was like it's time to go to bed so we all went to bed, but uh, it was your fun perfectly fun
Okay
Yeah, I know Jamie would kind of concern me after I fell asleep that ghost was maybe being inappropriate
But I know I got a message from Alex this morning saying she had fun, too. So
No, we had a good time. I mean Alex, I mean ghost was just being ghost Alex
Handled him. We've been in her talks for a while and you know, I mean, it was not it was good
It was I think it was good. I don't think Alex left upset or anything like that
somebody in the private chat
Just letting you know.
Okay, let me have a look.
Dr. Corn Dog, I don't know who that person is,
but let me see this.
Is he back, oh yeah, hold on,
there's somebody backstage and I don't know
if I met this guy.
I believe put your screen up.
Yeah, hello.
Hi, Psych, I mean, I've only been on your panel
about 17 times.
Hey, how did the pickle juice once you go?
Okay, it was disgusting. I vomited seven times. It was like it. I felt so bad for you, but you left it
I was like, yeah, I think he's really getting sick
We were you left us on a cliff. Thank you. We were he came over yesterday and he popped in for a second
I was laughing. He's like summer. I'm gonna give you the pickle
We were like, okay, so we were all hook bottom thinker and he took a drink
He was like look like he's very puke and he bounce. Yeah, I didn't I didn't disrupt your your
You're streamed too much, right?
I added a little-
No, no, no, no, no.
You were perfectly fine.
You were the only cool person
that would let me do a drink review on you.
Thank you so much.
Anytime, anytime.
You were perfectly fine.
I wanted to show you what I got.
I got the-
Ooh, Marci Deck.
Marci, I got the Marci Deck.
Do you have any opinions?
Oh, that's a great one.
That's one of the original deck.
Okay, cool.
If it's psyche-approved,
then I feel good about my purchase, okay?
Yeah, there you go. Oh dude. I need interject interject some real quick
Um, I'm 5 and 0 on sweet spots and some of the help me determine this shit is terror cars
I didn't do a I didn't like write nothing down
I just like grab the deck like pull a couple cards lately. It's been on fucking point, dude
That's all you got to do. That's all you got to do really just pull some cards. What do they mean to you? You know?
Yeah, what deck you got?
Oh, just a right a rider weight is the one I was using for that. That's my whole
It's been like a half moon is dirty as fuck on the edges
I haven't touched a shit and walk
But when I was looking into certain events are about to happen
I would just grab it and like pull a car even like do like a fan and like pull it out and like dude
It's been a
It's determined the loss and making a fucking money, dude
Really?
Yeah
And in the in the past I've in the past I've done like you know, I would write it down
I would use a certain custom spread and write frame everything a lot of times for making money shit
It wouldn't work, but other shit. It was always on point but lately
Numerous times now I would just grab this shit and think and pull it and it's like damn dude and it's been right for like
Three big three big major fucking things lately. That's dope Babylonian. That's awesome
Yeah, that means you're really pulling with intent and you're really you know, you're really speaking. Hey psyche
I'm gonna pull one card. Can you tell me what this card means? Sure
What is this the priestess the Empress
Okay, that's that it's let me see. It's three. It's number three. Okay. That is the
Empress. Yeah, the Empress. Okay. What does that mean? Yeah, the Empress is all the queen in the deck and like a lot of times that's a
the pregnancy card or it's like um oh shit there's fertility there oh god oh that's not good for me
i just i just yeah oh okay well thanks for telling me that that's good to know oh did you have a scare
i mean i'm i'm sleeping with my wife okay um psyche well listen to your wife sorry yeah what do you
I have the app and so this month on the app. It's eight dollars for the big Mac
Big Mac meal and I had a couple coffee a couple caramel caramel frappuccinos with that comes out to like 15 bucks
Save about five bucks using the app. I would say check out the app
It's pretty good some pretty good deal on it right on I well
I just came up to ask what you get on your McDonald's order and to show you my deck and thank you and summer
It's great to see you and Babylonian keep making money, baby
Thank you great to see you
All right, sweetie. Have a good day
Yeah, we've got some good people coming up today. I'm getting like you know last night I
Needled you know the field gate in the chat was a fake feel I kept saying you know I said how many dick pics
Did you send me you know just type in the back chat? Well, what is some of them were but one of them was not a fake
Okay
There was the real one in there. Yeah, there was a real one in there
Okay, well, I do but Alex usually uses his he has fake feel accounts. So that's usually who does that
Yeah, you know Alex just come up under your real name Alex and be yourself and I'll talk to you but
Alex McQueen of course, but I'm a little bit more
I'm tired of getting everything in my show with you know, and we're bombs and porn bombs
And so I have to be more careful. I need to at least know the person or
Make sure that they're legit. So
Right. Yeah. Yeah, I mean, that's what yesterday. No form bombs tonight. It was just a great show. I finally
Energy's getting right
You know
Just kind of you know, you know how it is
She's got to start speaking positive things because we focus on all the bad stuff. It's just gonna drive you nuts
Yeah, you know
You've given me a lot of really good advice, I want to thank you for always, you know, telling me like it is, you know, you do it unfiltered, you do it, you know, really from the bottom of your heart, if you're a little bit mad at me or not, like, you know, it's all good, tough love sometimes, or, you know.
Just know if I didn't care if I drew I do care about you psyche and I definitely want to see you know
I mean and I do appreciate that you know me well enough that even when I am kind of a brat
You know, I mean you can see past that and understand that it's only coming out of a place of carried
Not trying to control you not my thing. I just don't want to see you stressed. You know, I mean this is supposed to be fun
Yeah
I'm coming around a little bit, you know, I go I get in my low points and then sometimes like I get a little triggered and stuff like that
I'm working on myself and hopefully improving and I I really want to make it a fun experience
for everybody and comfortable for everybody in the chat and you know, I can't please everybody but
You know, I can try to
So bad Balonian you said you do some readings
Yeah, I've been doing tarot cards for a long time. Would you like to do a reading on me?
um I
Can pull yeah, I can pull a card real quick. Um, I have to open
I actually hang on I got an animal message. Let me do the animal message. I think animal message is right behind me
Hold on. Okay
I'm glad people are getting it to get more to tarot even if like some people have put it down and stuff like that
but it's always good to
You know
Like my my gift is big time to serve it right like I can that's a huge thing for me energy
I can read energy. It's it's what's kept me alive my whole life, right?
And I've thought about doing it just to see you know what I mean, but I don't know
Well, I've heard like it said that tarot is kind of like poker for women. It's like women sometimes have a natural
I mean, I think women are already the high priestess where they have this intuition
They don't really need the cards, but cards are always a good way to
Delete, you know to direct direct the reading maybe like, you know, yeah story line a little bit
So but there's all kinds of way you are very intuitive, you know
I think women most women have that gift because they have that receptive
Energy and that's definitely my gift for sure
I can and sometimes I hate it because you know and you understand what I'm saying like sometimes when you can fill it and you
Can fill energy and I can walk into her room and I can just be like, oh, okay. Here we go. It's like energy fucking
Yeah, other people's energy though, you know, I can always feel it. Yeah
Blessing in a curse. It can be a curse at times. Go ahead. Go ahead. Do I have a load here?
All right, these I've had some at parties I've had some insane things with these animal messages
I don't use that much the tip my my right away deck is in the other room. It's all like locked in the room right now, but
I pulled first the baboon in love and declarations of passion heartfelt
communications is the key and the beaver investing in home comforts provides
security and family togetherness.
That's pretty on point because that's what I did all that's what I've been doing
Especially all weekend. I kind of took some time offline didn't get on panels just kind of chilled at home
So the kids some time with my husband. So yeah, family's always a good thing. Good job. I
Like the other one from me see you Babylonian or alright alright sure
But these yeah, I've been in parties and did this shit and it was fucking insane and like like so like
Fucking like hilarious insane type shit, but even I
don't know
Like I don't know y'all. I don't know y'all but I did this I've done this shit like this is I rarely use this deck
But I have done it in the construction back fucking decades and it's been crazy like the shit that cars pull is fucking insane, dude
All right, let me uh
I'm gonna try to I'm trying to uh
Replicate what I did with the rider weight deck to get the shit that was like on point
recently
Do your thing do your thing
My favorite pussy ready
You're sorry
Give it to baby
No, man, he's over here stalking me. Let's be fed
You're in her
It's for every loud
But there I mean there was more to it read off the car there's a hole during the book has a hole more saying behind
You can read whatever you'd like
Yeah
But I'm a full I gotta go it was the the baboon and the beaver
I'm a I'm working on pulling up one for psyche or at least one
Last night, let's see page pulled one for me. I got the octopus
Kind of a interesting card. Hi, babe. Oh
Okay
Mr. Tricks and
Jamie the negativity last night
I really didn't act because you know I was in such a good mood that the negativity
I don't really notice as much, but I don't think even if ghosts was a little bit
You know, if you know his personality, you know, that's how ghost is, you know, and he doesn't mean any harm
He really doesn't he just likes to debate and stuff. It's sometimes he drives people a little bit crazy, but
He's a good heart basically it was his birthday. So I give him a little pass
All right, so first I pulled the beaver again, which is crazy
Investing in home comforts provides security and family togetherness and the elephant
You gain the love and wisdom that has passed from one generation to the next. Oh
I love that. I don't think I've ever pulled. I only have ever pulled the elephant before dude
Well, you know elephants are very you know elephants are the only animal
I think they mourn for the dead, you know, there's elephant graveyards and they mourn
They're also, you know in Hinduism. They're Ganesha. It's like the destroyer of obstacles and
They look kind of funny. They have that big trunk that's a little funny and they're sometimes afraid of mice and things like that.
Well, actually, in Hinduism, Ganesha rides a mouse. He's an elephant that rides a mouse. That's his vehicle.
So there's some different perspectives on it. But I definitely love the elephant energy.
You know, that's a great reading and it's like I really am investing in my home and my little family of cats and stuff
And also my my home here
This is kind of like my little home away from home and my
Love it. Thank you so much
Well, the elephant's crazy, dude. I don't like I've had epic readings. I don't think I've ever pulled the elephant before
Definitely I have an elephant. I have an elephant. I'm looking right at right now on my wall
I have a Ganesha
Little mandala on my wall. Wow. Awesome, dude
Well, thank you so much. That's glad you've been getting getting back into it and you know keep going and
You know, you're gonna be able to help a lot of people. I think
The awesome so tell me about your your screen name is the Babylonian like are you into ancient Babylon or what's that about?
Yes, I'm in an ancient Babylon, but it this began as like a multi-layered joke. Um
A long time ago, um
buddy
Well
I'm kind of a I'm into Babylon to you like the Babylonian hanging gardens and you know, it was like this one of this first
Yeah, I'm actually a professional. I'm actually a professional gardener and botanist
So, yeah, that does definitely have significance to me the hanging gardens of Babylon
But it has to do with the whole like the idea of what?
Like Jamaican Babylon's gonna fall but more at the
Simultaneously multiple levels like how people want to come out of Babylon, but yet they
They need it to survive. It was like a joke just to fucking troll people in the beginning
Interesting and that's why I changed the shit back. That's why I changed the shit back to the beginning so people recognized because I earlier I had fucking
My mom some more research. I was doing I changed the shit back to this because that's who I originally was under this channel was proud Babylonian
Well interesting I suggest everybody do some research into ancient Babylon there's Queen Samarama's right the
Babylonian king and she has top the Tom moves or we see what was her
She had a basically she's the original Venus and then she either had a son or a husband
That kind of is the cupid energy. So and then there's the Tower of Babel was was was which they wanted to like
communicate with God which is different. I mean divination they wanted to
Rise up to God
Yeah
Got so high and then God brings it down, right?
Yeah, I think that's crazy. I think the true meaning. I don't think anyone knows the true meaning and
That's something I've always been interested in. What's the true?
What actually is the true meaning behind the you know the Tower of Babel, you know
because if they're if if man was together as one and he wanted to communicate with God or like have a
Communicate have a be in the vicinity be close to fucking God. Why would God strike the shit down? You know late?
Right because it's like maybe it's kind of like how Lucifer wanted to be God instead of God or like you know
He wanted to be God and it's like
God kind of threw him down to the planet like oh you want to be God?
Why don't you just rule this planet yourself and see how easy it is to be God and you know
Maybe it's a little bit of a pride thing to trying to you know bring down man's pride a little bit
So they think they get we think they're more powerful than God at times, right or
You know
I mean, I've been into divination. I've been in a divination since I was like 16 years old
I played the Ouija board as a joke and it predicted a
multi-year sequence of events
Mm-hmm
Yeah, and so that's right down on the stuff right down the stuff too. Like, you know, see how it
See how it works out for you
You have it
Alright, it's written down. It's written down in my mind. I'll never forget that shit the one dude. It ran it ran out the fucking house
Well, that's pretty cool like I suggest keep going at it like at least pull a card a day for yourself
Sounds like it's working for you
No, well, I honestly think dude it might be it's just like a bust in the nuts
You don't need to bust a nut every day, dude
Like you don't need to pull a card every day depends on I guess it depends on where you're out in your journey and shit, you know
Learning if you're learning you can do to 10 readings a day, but like me lately
Like I didn't touch the ship for a while, but I just went all right
I'd have to make a decision now and I need some fucking help on what the fuck I need to decide and I pull out the fucking deck and do
A fucking I don't I don't write shit down. I just do pull a fucking card and bang dude
The shit was fucking right three times lately
Good and there was like big money riding on it
Yep, it can uh can definitely help in so many different uh different ways you can also like even chat chat
I'm gonna say and like like you said for me you need to familiarize yourself first with what's going on
You don't have to you can't like
You know you have to start when you're starting you have to do more readings and learn and you know familiarize yourself with what was what's going on
Yeah, when I started my I would get decks when I think I was like eight years old and I'd be like
Like can I read for your mom and then but then I would just be going out of the book
I'm almost like I'm almost like learn every car learn the meeting so you don't have to use the book
You know, she's she wanted she really wanted me to she's like she didn't care what I what I did
She just wanted me to be the best at it kind of thing right and that really
spurred me to like really try to
Like learn all the symbolism the meanings and to know it like the back of my hand and so you know
God bless parents can you know guiding guiding you the right direction, right?
Well, she's she encouraged you to do a more intuitive
type thing. Yeah, just to be able to like, you know
Read it read it without having to use a book like to know the cards well enough to well be able to
Yeah, some of these books are so crazy, dude
Like some of these books if you try to read them like they won't make no sense to half the people anyways
You know, and that's what that's what what that's what one of my
Mentors told me is like most of these books are worth this dude. Like you got a fucking
Look at this. He told me don't read the fucking books because it's a bunch of not it's you're not gonna understand it
You know, right? Well, it's like I studied a lot of occultism
And so it does tie together with astrology and the symbolism and things like that
But when it comes down to it, you can just look at the card and see what feeling you get from it and
That's why women are kind of better, I think naturally, is because they're more receptive
to these messages.
Men can be very left-brained, very logical about it, and very technical, and I've seen
great male readers, but I think the best readers are going to have a mixture of the
intuition and the technical knowledge of it.
Men are, you know, men are kind of more left-brain-oriented usually, women are a little more right-brain-oriented.
You know, it's always good to find the balance.
That's why I think I'm kind of at an advantage being gay is because a lot of I'm in touch with my feminine side pretty naturally,
but also my masculine side is being a man.
And so I can kind of do both.
I think, uh, I've gotten a lot of good feedback for kind of proving that to myself. So
Yeah, I've done it enough to have it without a shadow of a doubt
It's it works like I can say that works that even if you're not you know, don't believe in it
It will still work, you know, so
but I want to reiterate like
I want when I was hardcore in a sports speculation. I tried numerous times like I
I've got notebooks full of readings and sports speculation and a lot of times it didn't pan out
Like doing doing the whole like framed reading the whole like a frame
You know saying framing the inquiry putting down the things but I'm specifying recently
I didn't do none that shit. I just pulled out the deck
And mentally framed it in my mind and pulled the shit and it was like it's been on fucking point
Yeah, keep going with that and you know, you'll just get better and better and
Really the thing is you'll be able to help a lot of people too
And so as for sports betting, I don't know how great it is with sports betting. Sometimes I think
Go into it without you know, really like a material gain in mind
Because it really is you know a spiritual thing for the most part, but it can be effective I guess in
That's what that's what that's what some of these people told me is like basically it shorts out if you try to if you try to do like 3d
Financial gain it'll short out. They're trying to tell me oh, that's why that doesn't because it was a
Like hardcore
Revelatory and like I was having bad-ass readings except when I tried to apply it to make money
off a sports speculation
But that was when I was doing like, you know framing the shit writing it down, but just I
Don't know and in one of these people that try to tell me that I did the fucking animal message reading for her at a
Party and it was like fucking most time the most hilarious shit fucking ever, dude
Yeah, and it's like also I don't think there's anything wrong with like using a first aid entertainment purposes because
basically it should be
Partially for fun and just know the novelty and interests of it, but at the same time it deserves to be treated respectfully and
You know seriously and so you know a lot of people aren't into it for a lot of different reasons, but
You know even ghost was like, you know
He doesn't like tarot, but he was very happy with his animal card reading last night from page and you know, I think
Some people can be converted into at least respect for the tarot. So
Don't know what people are talking about in chat. Let's take the angry drunken door if I don't know what you're talking about
But okay interesting. Oh, I see the chats kind of got their own thing going on
So what's what's planned for today guys, which you got anything on the
Back okay, so you all right. Bye. Bye
I've always wanted to get into
runes, but I've never done it.
I've got, I have a, I have a
rune tarot card deck, but it's
like complicated and shit.
I have barely, barely, I think
I've mused it maybe three times,
but it's like,
it's a very,
it's more, it's more complex
or. Yeah, well, it's
like mystical and complex and
shit. It's like not
Well runes, okay, so runes are like, you know, there's like the Nordic Nordic religion, you know Odin Odin
Actually was hanging from a tree upside down
I don't know if you got I think he hung himself
but he upside down on a tree just like the hangman card and he came up with all the runes, right and
These are very powerful magical symbols with a lot of meaning and it's like a new alphabet basically the magical alphabet you can
Learn some of the meetings and you know, you'll also get some revelations about things
But it does take time to to learn them all. I would say focus on one thing at a time
Yeah, I should be I should have used that I mean, I I
Definitely should have tried it more than I did but I haven't even fucked with it lately
But you got time to you got time to learn it, you know
But it's based on the runes, but it's um, it's from it's from glory and org
It's like what they claim is like the real teachings of Jesus like the real original freemasonic shit
So yeah, I'm familiar with that website that is that is gonna be Gnostic the Gnostic
Gnostic tradition and so they go into a lot of different
Different traditions that kind of encompasses everything but the the Gnostic right glory is actually a great website
they got some great tutorials on there and
I recommend everyone checking that website out. It's
Got a lot of information a lot of information, right? Yeah. Yeah, I am yeah
well, that's do and
One of the things they talk about
It's very simple, but it's a I think there's something to it
I think that might be the reason that was um what what they call fornication like they're their definition of fornication
Hey, psyche. Hi
Hey, miss funky. We got um, we're here with proud Babylonian this I want to get a card from proud Babylonian
But before then can you ban thing that is from your chat because he's the one that was posting part of my information on
Beatus chat and now he's harassing me in your chat and I feel like I can't come in here and enjoy myself anymore because of him
okay i mean and uh are you you're a mod too right and so yeah but i can't i can't like get
rid of them get rid of them without i think i feel like you should do that okay it's done
thank you you're welcome hi proud Babylonian may i have an animal card if it's not too much
I think uh, yeah, I love these animal cars. I don't use them that I haven't used them that much, but I love animals
I feel like I have spent many lives as an animal, so I'm curious to see what you're gonna pull
These cars are like brand new I don't for a long time I barely use them, but um
Some of the readings have been what it was me like okay, let's do I'm gonna I'm
beginning to show the cars thinking of a new spunky but I was gonna tell you like uh one of the first rings
I did was was someone that at the point time was my best friend who was in the process of becoming my worst enemy
And uh, I did an animal ring for both of us and it was like hardcore like
You know, it's funny proud Babylonian. Have you ever noticed that some of the people become the closest people in your life?
You have a major altercation with in the beginning. Have you ever noticed that?
I have and I noticed that like all like some people who've become like, you know, just just
Major in my life the first interaction with them or whatever may not be like the best interaction
And we have to overcome something together and then like somehow our power struggle
Turns into this bonds like he's grinning over it. I know he knows what I'm talking about like you get that man
Yeah, it happens in lots of different ways. I mean even in a fucking
Like dudes a lot of times dudes that will get in a fight like they're fucking yeah
I gotta they gotta fight it out and then and women are the same way
I I really am only referring to women honestly in my life like we got to like duke it out
Emotionally and then when we do it's like fine and then when we become like super bonded. It's awesome
Well, it's about respect. I mean they they respect
On a on a very street a base level like 3d base level thing dudes that have no no spiritual concept or anything
like they respect the fact that the other dude fought them hand-to-hand and
Gave them a challenge so they respect on a three-dimensional level and on a spiritual level. It's even more of
Complexion shit it becomes more bonded
I agree with that it's funny right but it's also funny I have you guys ever had
like a best friend breakup with you like say they don't want to talk to you
anymore and be done with you yeah that is like more painful than any breakup divorce
Anything I've ever had in my life, man, that is so hurtful.
It is amazing the power of how much of a good friend
and the love that you have for them,
how deep it runs and how different it is
than like a romantic thing.
Like it's crazy.
Alright Proud Babylonian sorry for babbling on no I'm listening. I was the hardcore thinking about what you said
Yeah, you ever happen man
I'm fucking almost 50 years old. I've had lots of friends become
40 I know man, it's like
And not even become an enemy just be like I don't want I don't want your energy in my life anymore
That is like the most hurtful thing and most of the time for when it's it's only a woman
That's ever done this to me and it was because of a man
And I was warning her about that man and some shit that I had like heard and she was like all in she's like
No, I'm I'm marrying this guy. This is happening and I was like why I heard xyz about this guy
They saw him having dinner with a girl and he said he was supposed to be at work and all this and she didn't believe me
And she was like I'm done with you. You're just poison and you're trying to ruin my relationship
Well, she ended up coming back 10 years later two kids later and said like I'm sorry you were right
And I should have believed you the whole time
And I'm accepted our friendship back. It's not the same, but it man. That was a hard breakup
Hard hard
Yeah, and it's like how time heals all right like time
Well, you know like it'll never heal us to get us back to the place that we were but we're we are friends now and it is just amazing how
You know in the moment someone tries to protect you and you're so
sold on something like you're so convinced that you could never think that somebody was like trying to look out for you that it's only like
Yeah, sorry man
I feel exactly what you're saying it was it was the um
Look, I've been married a bunch of times and divorced a bunch of times and there's nothing more painful
I've gone through than that like that friendship loss was was epic
Hi Christine. You can't it's impossible to go back because y'all are two different people back there
It's the whole thing. Yeah, and we grew into different people too
But like at least you know, it's the trust me now, you know
But you can never step in the same river twice
familiar with rivers, but I
I own property by a crazy-ass river and
You can't step in the same river twice. Yeah, it's never the same never the same again
I
Pulled the beaver again, dude. This is insane dude. What is the game?
Okay, the second card is the crab I pulled the beaver in the craft
Oh, that's kind of funny because my son's nickname is crab in so I think that that's very epic that you pulled that
Well the beaver just means investing. I haven't read I need to okay. I pull the shit three times
I have to read the shit off the book. Yeah, read it out read it out
I want to know okay beaver investing in home conference provides security and family togetherness
Beautiful that's something I need more of in my life. All right, so this is the third time. This is insane dude. I've never
Like I've never pulled three cars fucking the same car three fucking time. Okay, the beaver
Gotta find this shit in the book and read this you and maybe the beaver's trying to give you a message
No, I'm not trying to be rude. I'm just saying no
Yeah, no, I'm sorry. I believe I believe you a hundred percent now. Yeah, I'm pretty intuitive, too. So
Yeah, this message if it's three it's gotta be for me
Yeah, you need to take it as hard as long as I do too
All right, let me find this
That's crazy, man, and I'm not an odd um, it's nice to meet you man. I don't think I've seen you on a panel before
Yeah, I haven't seen Babylonian a while, but yeah, and Hebrew hammer and Babylonian on today, so yeah, I'm relatively new around here
It's been a couple months for me, so
I was trying to find this in the book. Um, but yeah, that's insane that I pulled the same thing three times the way that in the method
I did it
And what we the it says investing in home conference provides security and family togetherness which is my family's all fucked up
I mean, I've been open about that forever
Mine too, man. Don't feel bad. You know some of the best people come from the most fucked up places, right?
Okay. Here it is. Here's the beaver. Glossy beaver, councils, conservation and all senses of the word.
From protection, the earth's resources for future generations to freeing yourself from large projects to that sap your vigor and leave you vulnerable.
Beaver remains monogamously for life.
Beautiful.
Keeps her offspring safe until the call of the wild
Bids them leave
Although our lives may be very different the archetypal family unit still haunts our dreams. Oh
Beers lessons is that you turn
Longing into reality and transform love into a way of life
I can't even tell you like on panel how much that resonates with me. So that's cool, man
I hope it resonates with you, too
And you pulled that for me too and for summer
Thank you man, that's just crazy dude. What does the crab mean?
Well, I got a hold of a second. I see my both families off my family's been all fucked up for
Yeah, forever
Well, yeah, I mean since this is my incarnation is specific blood blister. Yeah, I feel you man
I've got this deep urge longing whatever to create my own family and it's like just never worked out
And I mean, like a family unit, you know, like a man, a woman, our children, we raise them together and like it just, it just continuously does not work out for me and that is my, the bane of my existence.
So.
Well, I wish you the best in that, Spunky, I think maybe this is the time, you know, this is maybe, I think...
Thank you, I do, too.
Yeah.
I really do, too. I've never, uh, I've never felt this way about anybody else before. I've never
loved another person's child so much before. Um, I hope it can just, you know, roll into
manifest into my reality. That would be amazing.
I think like things happen for a reason and that's like maybe they didn't work out before so they could work out now
You know, I think it's like yeah, I've said that same exact thing to Justin that like, you know
I know we're old but you know everything else didn't work out for us before because we needed to be right here
Where we are now and you know, we're both wild and crazy
And we had to get like our shit out of our blood and our veins to be able to like appreciate being monogamous and being with one
One another and that sort of thing, you know
Yep
Yeah
The I wonder do do beavers really made for life though. That's how they do they do I've heard that too
That's crazy. I mean like I respect like you know, there's even fish that do it, you know, there's birds
There's fish
Penguins Penguins Penguins I heard made for life and I can look up right now. What is for life
Is there a main woman in your life proud if you can say so? Oh, no, I'm not even close. I've been a
I have been a hermit for a long ass motherfucking time, but maybe maybe I mean someone's coming for you in the future
Well
I'm definitely open to it. I mean I used to be a ladies. I used to be a ladies man
I'm not it's not that I'm awkward with women. I've had a
Lots of women lots of options, but for a long time now. I've been a straight-up hermit
Well, yeah, I enjoyed the idea of romance and fucking love
But I'm I am on a higher intellectual plane than most people and if that sounds arrogant or whatever
I'm cool with that, but no, I am I will tell you I feel the same way and I
Had this like come to Jesus moment or come to the universe moment where I was like look
Can you just bring me somebody who's like on my level?
Like can you like I'm ready and when I got myself mentally ready. That's when they showed up and I still don't think I was really ready, but
You know, it's working out good. It's been a year and a half and like life is really good together
And I hope you get that same thing man. I hope it just falls in your lap like it did for me
Awesome it that's great. I mean I got goosebumps a couple times which is weird
Like I don't usually get goosebumps fucking around on YouTube, but it happened
Sorry, I'm real real like I just like say it like it is and
Life life is like that, you know in life is short
And if I feel like I have some wisdom to impart on somebody else like it's resonating with you
And that's the goosebumps man, so just be open. That's all the universe is be open
Yeah, yeah, yes, definitely, but also like I have to be you have to be suspicious too late, but
Time be more open I understand after
After three be after three beavers does I'm gonna put a little note to be open for a certain time
Cautiously optimistic man. That's the key to life. You got to be cautiously optimistic. You know what that means
Yes, yeah, you got it. Like you just you just guard yourself
But like have your heart open a little bit don't let everybody in there obviously
But just like you know have that beautiful spirit about you that is open to things than letting the universe in but then like you know
Screen it before it comes all the way in
Well, I mean, that's kind of how I am by nature.
I mean, I moved to an insane fucked up place
because of a prophetic dream that was in fucking sane
and most of us come true.
Yeah, I have those dreams too.
That's kind of funny that we're talking right now.
I've had...
Very prophetic dreams
Having to do with people that come into my life
And then I'm able to help them and do things which is great
And I've also had like dreams about people that things weren't
Going to not go so good and that I couldn't help and that's an awful feeling
It's
It's made me believe in spirituality and like made me reach out into the the unknown and what
else is out there because I would call myself at one point you know being some sort of atheist and
now I am completely not like I believe in so much more and um you know I think I'll just be
Wow, that's awesome. Yeah, I understand the feeling like it's almost like a rebellion or rejection like if there was a God
Then how could all this horrible should happen? Yeah, I had a real rough childhood
And it really made me like shut down and that kind of thing
but I'm I'm you know, like I said, I'm 40 now and I like it's completely different and I
Spend my life trying to open the hearts of other people. I think that are kind of closed and beat down by life, too
I don't think that life is meant to hurt you. I think it's meant to learn from it, you know
learn learn learn what the burn is causing yeah learn from the burn yeah
learn from the burn and more ways than one my friend yeah yeah I mean that you
like if you lift weights because I used to be hardcore in the body sculpting
And it's not exactly comfortable, but no, it's not like there's a lot of things that hard work can teach you
What is that psyche? Oh, let's talk it two people are in the chatter. Just talk it. I was showing asterisk
I got time on and they're saying oh, there's some nasty messages being sent behind the scenes
You know Vicky is not a bad person and for this like if people are saying I'm harassing Vicky
You are sadly mistaken. Yeah, I don't think you're asking Vicky like
She wants to turn me straight.
It's not an easy thing.
Vicki has easily amused.
You caught her eye.
She wants to harass you.
Like, that's all that is.
So I'm fine with Vicki, you know?
And I'm fine with all those people, you know?
It's just like, you know, I hope they...
It's just a little simple, you know infatuation and she wants to show you her titties. That's all and I know it's gross
if nobody wants to see that but
That's what that's about. I think I think it's uh, I don't think it's in it from a nefarious place
You know what I mean? No, and I wish you know, I'm not gonna harass any of those people or like, you know
I'm not going to go to anybody else's level and, you know, when you wrestle with pigs, you know,
a pig enjoys it and you get dirty, right? You get money. You don't need to get money.
Hey, Babylonian, can you tell me what the crab means? Yes, yes, I can. I have it right now.
Crab, show your emotions and regenerate love. A crab's whole being is synchronized to the waxing
So are your body's hormonal and physiological systems tuned to the world's circulation rhythms.
Or circadian rhythms.
Yeah.
Live in harmony with those.
Live in harmony with these and your whole being will thrive.
Crab is protected by a rigid carapace, but to grow she must risk molting her armor, becoming soft and vulnerable.
Like crab, garner courage and take that risk, be it sporting, trial, mental task, or emotional revelation, which offers you regeneration and emotional flowering.
Well, if that ain't me, I don't know what else is I got the armor up
And I need to shed it to let someone in to be nice, you know, and I'm
I'm a little
Calus
But that there we form Calus is for a reason in shit, you know, mm-hmm
Yeah
It's hard it's hard to know when to let someone in if they're the right person or not, you know
that's such a vulnerable thing and
You know you you like keep touching the hot stove and getting burned and you're like why do I keep doing this?
But like maybe one time the stove won't be on right?
I always see lately. I've been seeing the people Indian like people sticking their hand in grease and pulling out the fried food
Like I think that's just like wrong. I don't want to be I don't want to be that numb ever
No, and I don't think it's about being numb. I think it's about just timing, you know
Well, I mean yeah timing out I definitely believe in timing timing is everything
Timing is everything, but some people say time doesn't exist. So
Timing and time is two different things like timing has to do with like the rhythm. There's there's definitely a rhythm of life
Maybe time doesn't exist. I think it does but timing is magical and
Purposeful and you know, I think there's a time for everything. I think it's your time Babylonian
Well, I know I do know that uh with the
Expert timing you can defeat a much more capable opponent like this dude's badass and shit
But if you sit back and you you recognize everything and just wait for the right time
You could lay this you could lay him out. You could defeat your opponent easily
Yep, sometimes you got to lay low, stay cool, strike when the iron's hot, you know, like
Start with all these hot and cold references, but
Well, you know and hot and cold are like, you know, they're it's on a pole. It's a polarity, right?
They're actually they're just they're just degrees of temperature, right? Just like there's really no past
There's really no future. There's always all we have is the present moment. That's where the power
I'm saying you always have is right here right now. That's all we have control of at least yes
Is the right here and the right now and that's where I try to live all the time
Just try to like control your moment control how you're treating other people control. What's
What's done to you, you know, you can't really but like this exact moment you can you can defend yourself you can
You can start planning for the future, but what's gonna actually happen it unfolds, you know
Yeah, I mean, I always try to treat I always try to treat everyone with respect even even when I can see in their eyes
Like I live I live in but fuck Egypt. I don't know if they know about that
but I
Live in but fuck Egypt and so there's a lot of fucking real I
Don't be judgmental, but there's people that are like off way off and shit, you know on a different
But I always respect them even though you know, whatever. Yeah
So there's some real real low vibrational energy in the world
And you just have to like smile and nod and respect them and let them move on and get out of your your field, you know
I'm sorry about the first time I heard about the BFV I didn't even I didn't know what it was
But this is I went to high school in it money
Yeah, this girl was so gorgeous. So gorgeous to so beautiful to this day
I still dream if I could I want to talk to her again
but um, she told me she's gonna be a feeling like where the fuck is that and
It's when I ended up moving to where she was from. That's where I live right now. Oh
Is she around?
No, no, she is missing. She's been in my for 30 years, but
Her in bread family is from here
And um, it's uh, is she really MIA like a missing person or no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, she just would she she's not on any of these social media groups or something like that. Yeah
The best people aren't on social media
But I I know I'm in the buying this property here where she was from and I also bought a property off the tax
Trust list where where where the neighborhood where she used to live when we went to high school together
It's like weird, but there's all type of weird crazy shit from where I live now to where I grew up. I mean
That's like this like uh, it's just not normal. There's all type of whack-ass crazy shit
Go ahead dude like
I was just letting everybody know that I'm on I'm also streaming on Twitch right now
And if you would like to it says free channel subscription with Prime
See if you're on Prime Amazon Prime you get a free
Twitch subscription, but you can also have the ability to pick one channel and I'm subscribed to get a free membership to it
And so if you'd like to subscribe to mine, you're welcome to I'm gonna post my
Twitch link in the in the chat, but if you're on them if you're on
on Twitch or on Amazon Prime you get a free one and so I'm sorry that's just a little
short commercial announcement, but good
Okay, but the last time I was on here that I think
No, the two or three times before the last time that one dude MC nemesis was on here when I was on here
And he came on my thing earlier today and he spoke intelligently
About some things. Um, he can't he can but you know, he's he has an anger
Disorder like where he's as explosive
Intermittent disorder where he will start saying the n-word and so I can't really have him on my pan
That's what he that he's he typed that shit in my
No, he's good. No, he's doing something different dude. He doesn't have
He said that shit in my back chat first
But I had to let him on because he spoke he's the only person I've come across on YouTube that spoke and tells me on a certain
Topic, do you have a panel that you do Babylonian?
Yeah, yeah, can can we post your link in the chat? I'm gonna subscribe
I have one too if you ever want to join. No, I would look I'm always looking for other people's panels
Yeah, I'm just like a bullshit hangout place. I don't do much, but like I'd love to have you
I
Try to be cool my number one thing
I try to prioritize honesty and truthfulness and that's what even talking to emcee nemesis day
Like talk about some crazy like we got to define terms
I think that's prop part of the problem with the world today is people just say all this shit
They don't even know what they're talking about like
Have a serious communication these days. We actually have to take time to define the terms we're utilizing because
People are just throwing all this wack shit that they don't even know what the fuck's going on
Yeah, it's bad
Okay
Let's see. Yeah, did you do you check in last night? We had a Alex on the panel. We had a really good panel last night
I didn't I miss it. It was fun. It was kind of later at night, but
You know put me in a better mood and we you know it goes to we had summer and Alex up having some good conversations
You know, I think I'm in a little bit of a better mood. And so so thank you Alex also Alex
Alexandra
always a pleasure to have you on the show and
I really recommend everyone checking out her channel. I'll try to get her
Her channel posted to you. She has a really cool news network on
But my show is crazy, man, I'm I don't abide by nobody's rules
I put my toe in the background psych you don't have to put my shit up because I say hardcore shit and
It's like you don't have to serve my shit. We don't but the the girl on
Check and see my link in the back if she wants to
Hey
What's the name again?
Will you put the thing down so I can see his name? I can't see you. Yeah, I'm sorry. Yeah. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I don't want to call the raw um
Okay, so did you does anybody ever told you that you sound like that guy that you were just talking about it's so funny
They hear you talked about it in third party cuz I man you guys are like twins. I wasn't gonna bring it up
But there will be a really super duper cool right now, but I'm just saying y'all sound like
No, you're funny. You're trying to be funny is what you're doing. I'm not I'm not actually I'm not I promise you
Even if you are you're being super cool today, so I don't give a shit, you know what I mean
You all
Think I sound like
Obviously MC Nemesis, right? No, I don't sound like you
Well, that's who you reminded me of as soon as I heard you but I don't care because I've been super duper cool
No, it's because you're okay number one your ears are broken
My ears are broken. Why are you here? I'm not being like so to you. I'm not. Oh, I'm I'm being honest
I'm telling you your ears are absolutely my ears are broken. I know
Listen, I'm telling you your ears are broken. Oh
I sound absolutely nothing what you're you're hearing you must be from a different geographical region and you hear is a
Southern twang
And associate is the other time I'm from southern the south. Okay. So again, not that either
That's hilarious. I don't sound nothing like mc nimble
So, like I said, either way, it doesn't matter to me whether you are or you're not.
Okay, so, yeah, basically what you're saying is cool.
But calm down.
Hey, calm down.
Call your nuts.
I haven't raised my voice or anything.
My wavles are fucking in Mucho County.
Well, they sound like they're getting a little tight.
So, yeah, no, they're, yeah, exactly.
They're getting tight.
They're getting hot.
They're getting, look at that.
Calm down.
Calm down, Dave.
No, I'm calm.
I'm calm.
There's no reason. I mean, I don't know if you know me, but I can definitely lose my shit and I have not done that at all
I've been actually really cool with you because again
Super cool today. Your name is summer. Your name is summer. So it's like your name is winner, you know
Yeah, no, my real name is actually summer. So there's that
Yeah, and my real name is the has nothing new the MC. No, but that's fucking that's fucking hilarious
That shows summer on it cuz I don't have to lie. I believe you 100% but see my problem
Is that I don't sell anything like MC?
Well, the fact that you're like so in your feet fees about it right now is make a feet evenly more towards that
You do probably sound like him
But either right again, you're being
Do you know who I'm talking about no, honey, no disrespecting I got every
Every reason to be in my feet fees and oh, yeah, he's a whole piece of shit, right? I mean he is kind of a piece shit
He goes to the regs everybody panels. He's banned from like everywhere
So I definitely wouldn't want to be him if I was you but I'm just saying y'all kind of sound like
That's all okay, kind of you you're from the south and you still think I have like that. I
Don't want to use a certain word, but that's like um
I don't know
Have you listened to recording yourself and you are you know the first time I heard myself as a youngster
I was like I sound like a fucking retarded redneck like I don't sound like that, right?
But I don't sound as retarded and in whatever the fuck MC Nemesis sounds like
But you have your opinion do you hear me you think I sound like him then I just sound like him a little bit
Man, that's called bullshit. I think you're fucking with me. I'm not I could
Billion different things if I wanted to but that's not what I was doing cuz again, you're being cool
So I mean
If you are you're him or not, you know, it's like I appreciate, you know, you're not using the n-word
Right. Oh, but listen, dude. Oh, I just I just talked to MC Nemesis dude. The reason I stopped using the n-word
Is where I had a dream I had a dream a hardcore dream that I knew was significant and I stopped using the n-word
Well, that's good, but you said you just talked to him and again
I only reason I haven't said anything because you brought him up and you kind of keep like read him up
So I think it's cool like because I just I just I just talked to him
Tell him I'm up here.
Yeah, Tom's coming to say hi.
No, well, he, I don't, I don't know him like that.
He came, he comes to my apartment.
You just talked to him, but you don't know him yet.
I never had a problem, I never had a problem with you.
He threatened to come like a physically assault me one time
and then that's when I had a problem with you after that.
But you just talked to him.
No, I like because he said he had he said something intelligent on a certain topic that no one ever ever on
It was has to do with Freemasons and shit
Well, I don't know if I'll solve this today, but you know what? It's like, uh, I don't care if people come under alts as long as they stick to their, uh...
They behave, right?
Yeah, they stick to the new personality.
Yeah, like I said, he was rude.
If you're on your meds and you're on the good old, that's okay.
No, I think it's funny, dude.
We cool with that.
I think it's funny, dude.
Like, yeah, she wants to call me MC Nemesis.
I think that's fucking hilarious.
I didn't call you that.
I think I said you sound like him a little bit.
That's what I said.
Yeah.
I think she has asked you.
Yeah, that's all that's all that and said it doesn't matter to me either way because you're being super cool
But like now you're not a little bit fighting
You're being a little weird, but you get you just talked to somebody you can't have come on the panel because you don't know
So, I mean, you know, it's
Whatever you can say that actually
No, I didn't I don't know I don't know him like haven't come on the panel. He just joined the thing
I don't give a fuck about none of that. I think it's funny
That you're pressing me about I think that's hilarious. You're the one that keeps dragging it. I would we would already been on something else
Are you got the beaver card too?
I'm with the beat all the beat three beavers and they're pressing me on this. That's hilarious, dude
That's fucking hilarious. That's cuz we're we're hard
Pressing you dude. Chill the fuck out calm down. It's okay. It's not that fucking serious. No, it's president
No, it is serious. You call me MC nemesis. That's some serious
Why are you hanging on to this cuz these are just goddamn fee fees is he's fucking emotional
How am I not gonna get that that puts me my feet. I don't know anything. I said you sell my
Yourself an animal card right now
I'll pull my to pull myself an animal car there we go. Yeah
Who am I who am I who are you when I got
When I got
Those beavers
Calling you fragile. That's actually what I'm calling you. You're really being like the most
Who am I who am I he's fragile you're gonna get a bird card birds are fragile. Oh
We gotta see come on. I feel I'm feeling this and uh, whoa, dude
I got y'all. I think it was spunky that gave me goosebumps twice. Yeah
spunkies a weirdo
Oh
Who am I who am I listen you got that juju you gonna pull the right card right now? I know it
I'm not I got it. I gotta feel it. I gotta feel the right card
Over the camera
Seriously
summer summer it's hilarious if you know me you would know that I think it's
not really so I just said that you all sound familiar that's it so listen listen
listen it's not it's not serious you're riding a broken fucking horse
to me is funny as fuck I think it's fucking hilarious oh you're not laughing
you're being extra well then no one would believe it if I was like
What is it? What is it? Tell me the card. What's your card? I got it. I got to find the right car here
No, you do pull it you pull a card. You don't
Is the third one in the deck right now
The third one
Okay, the third the third one for right now, but I'm pulled to okay one
two
Three that's the third one
I'm face down. I'm not looking at I'm pulling another one first. No. No pull the third one. What is it?
Are you pulled the third one? I'm pulling a little firm
Okay, so I got the uh
wait
The moose and the other one was
Good card. Oh well
So the well no no the dolphin and the moose
The dolphin moose
You're a hybrid
So definitely pull some new cars today the dolphin
Which was the third car she said pull the third car dolphin
tune into the rhythm of your breath to find stillness and patience the moose is
Let's rely on some measure patience adversity will be overcome
Perfect.
The adversity will be overcome.
And guess what?
I have a dolphin tattooed on me.
Polar.
Oh, is it on your butt?
No, it's on my ankle.
Oh.
That Italian flag is the one.
My intuition is off.
Yeah, no, I have the Italian flag on one butt cheek
and the Cuban flag on the other butt cheek.
That's what I have.
I have kiss marks on my butt cheek.
Mm-hmm, yep.
Of course.
I didn't have lips, but I got them tattooed over with the flag.
I got Justin's lip tattooed on my butt.
there you go. I like that. So yeah, I think that was a perfect card for you right now.
Patience. Patience. I want to read this. I mean, these are, I mean, pull a lot of new
cars a day. I don't use these cars that often, but it would have been a lot of new ones.
The dolphin says tune into the rhythm of your breath to find stillness of patience.
Okay, let me see. All right. That's your last advice of the day. Okay, let me see. One, two, three.
13, 14, and 17, the cheetah.
I don't know a decision once made will be followed by unwavering action
Yeah
Yeah, that's some holy mother fucker
No, that's for real that's for real that's who actually am like when I actually make my decision like
If I said I will sit back for fucking 10 years 12 and wait on it
Old girls town y'all sit back for some 46 motherfucking years
But when lightning strikes like the cheetahs fast and shit niggas ain't fucking around
You know, it's funny. I got cheetah print tattooed on my forearm, too
Awesome
It's saying something to you something's coming for you Babylonian
Oh, it certainly is it certainly is like I oh
It's what's been happening. I mean
It's on the move it's coming for you get ready. Are you ready?
I've been ready. I've been right now. You think you're ready, but I don't think you're ready ready
Well, I used to be more ready. I'm now I got to I got I was to watch the day's the cold, right? You gotta get you gotta
Prepare yourself you're about to be hit
Yeah, I was too ready for too long, you know, so now I'm not even chillin and now it's gonna get you
When you stay ready for so long, it's just like you just staying ready and like yeah
Now lightning is gonna strike and you ain't gonna know what to do
You know, it's first nature when lightning strikes our homies
Yeah, I love you guys. I'm gonna take a little break and do some stuff, but you guys hear me, okay? Yeah, yeah, we hear you
Thanks to me. I'll see you again. Okay, and everyone in the chat. I'll be back tonight
I just got to take care of some stuff and get a little rest, but uh, love you guys. Thank you Spunky
Thank you summer Babylonian. Thank you Hebrew hammer and everybody else in the chat. I love you guys, and I'll see you soon
Okay, love you. Thank you. Bye honey. Love you. Bye Babylonian. Have a good night. All right. Have a good night
You guys later
Oh